Finding Aid for William Edward Beach photographs, 1931-1948
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
William Edward Beach photographs 1931-1948
Beach, William Edward
(in 5 boxes)
2.5 linear feet
92745 Ua 2
William E. Beach was an amateur photographer whose photographs document his hometown of Howell, Michigan and historical sites in other Michigan communities. His collection consists of photographic negatives (with some prints) and albums with prints of historic plaques and markers, statues of famous statesmen and their gravesites, early school buildings, historic houses, gristmills, sawmills, and county courthouses.
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The negatives (boxes 1-4) were donated by Barbara Stoner (donor no. 6201 ) in October 1982. The albums (box 5) were donated by the Howell Area Archives, Howell Carnegie District Library (donor no. 1284 ) in February 1999.
No further additions to the records are expected.
The collection is open to research.
William E. Beach, an insurance salesman, was an avid amateur photographer, interested in historic sites in Michigan and the eastern U.S. Beach covered the entire state of Michigan and photographed many small towns and villages.
He also documented the daily life of his hometown, Howell, Michigan, and photographed street scenes, delivery trucks, new buildings and roads under construction, gas stations, parades, storm and fire damage and prized possessions such as a car or a cow. Beach was also an active Mason and photographed many Masonic events and temples throughout the state. His photographs serve as candid documents of life in a small town in Michigan in the 1930's and 1940's.
The William E. Beach collection consists of photographic negatives (with some prints) and albums with prints of historic plaques and markers, statues of famous statesmen and their gravesites, early school buildings, historic houses, gristmills, sawmills, and county courthouses. Other subjects include tourist sites in Michigan (such as Greenfield Village or Mackinac Island) and state parks, especially those in the Upper Peninsula. His hometown of Howell, Michigan is also heavily documented.
The Beach collection is arranged into three series. In the Kodak series the negatives measure 2 3/4 by 4 1/2 inches in size and cover the years 1931 to 1948. The Leica series consists of 35-millimeter strips and were taken between the years 1936 and 1938. The third series consists of seven albums of carefully identified photographs.
An item-level listing of the contents of the Kodak and Leica series is available at the library. To aid researchers a geographic and subject index has been created and is attached to this finding aid. These indices provide the best introduction to the collection.
Beach created the photograph albums around broad topics, and each has a title. The albums include: "Michigan Historic Places," "Around Lake Erie in Ontario. Trip to Chicago Century of Progress," "Michigan Courthouses," "Michigan Ships, Monuments, Historic Places, Buildings, Creek Scenes," "Indian and Trail Markers," "Around Michigan: Historic Places, Buildings, Mills, Dams, Bridges, Masonic Buildings," and "Michigan Governors' Homes, Michigan Trees, Old Buildings of Michigan." The photos in the albums include Beach's negative number.
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Acme (Mich.); Ada (Mich.); Adrian (Mich.); Airports--Michigan.; Alberta (Mich.); Albion (Calhoun County, Mich.); Allegan (Mich.); Allen (Mich.); Alma (Mich.); Alpena (Mich.); Animals--Michigan.; Ann Arbor (Mich.); Athens (Mich.); Atlas (Mich.); Automobiles--Michigan.; Automobile service stations--Michigan.; Bad Axe (Mich.); Baldwin (Mich.); Barns--Michigan.; Battle Creek (Mich.); Bay City (Mich.); Beach family.; Belding (Mich.); Benton Harbor (Mich.); Bessemer (Mich.); Beulah (Mich.); Big Rapids (Mich.); Birmingham (Mich.); Blaney Park (Mich.); Bridges--Michigan.; Brighton (Mich.); Burns (Mich.); Byron (Mich.); Cadillac (Mich.); Calumet (Mich.); Cambridge Junction (Mich.); Capac (Mich.); Cass City (Mich.); Cassopolis (Mich.); Centreville (Mich.); Charlotte (Mich.); Charlevoix (Mich.); Cheboygan (Mich.); Chelsea (Mich.); Chesaning (Mich.); Churches--Michigan.; Clarenceville (Farmington Hills, Mich.); Climax (Mich.); Clinton (Lenawee County, Mich.); Cohoctah (Mich.); Coldwater (Mich.); Constantine (Mich.); Copper Harbor (Mich.); Corunna (Mich.); Courthouses--Michigan.; Cross Village (Mich.); Croton (Mich.); Crystal Falls (Mich.); Dearborn (Mich.); Deer Creek (Mich.); Delhi (Mich.); Delta Township (Mich.); Detroit (Mich.); Dexter (Mich.); Dimondale (Mich.); Dowagiac (Mich.); Dryden (Mich.); Dukes (Mich.); Dundee (Mich.); Dunsville (Mich.); Duplain (Mich.); Durand (Mich.); Dwellings--Michigan.; Eagle Harbor (Mich.); Eagle River (Mich.); East Lansing (Mich.); East Tawas (Mich.); Eaton Rapids (Mich.); Edenville (Mich.); Elsie (Mich.); Escanaba (Mich.); Esrey Park (Mich.); Farmington (Mich.); Festivals--Michigan.; Flat Rock (Mich.); Flint (Mich.); Fort Wilkins (Mich.); Fowlerville (Mich.); Frankfort (Mich.); Freemasons--Michigan.; Fruitport (Mich.); Galesburg (Mich.); Gladwin (Mich.); Glen Eden Park (Mich.); Glen Lake (Leelanau County, Mich.); Goodrich (Mich.); Grand Haven (Mich.); Grand Ledge (Mich.); Grand Rapids (Mich.); Grayling (Mich.); Green Oak (Mich.); Greenville (Mich.); Grindstone City (Mich.); Grosse Ile (Mich.); Hamburg (Mich.); Harbor Beach (Mich.); Harrison (Mich.); Harrisville (Mich.); Hart (Mich.); Hartland (Mich.); Hartwick Pines State Park (Mich.); Hastings (Mich.); Hell (Mich.); Hersey (Mich.); Hillsdale (Mich.); Holland (Mich.); Homer (Mich.); Horton (Mich.); Houghton (Mich.); Howell (Mich.); Hubbell (Mich.); Hudson (Mich.); Hudson Mills (Mich.); Huron City (Mich.); Indians of North America--Michigan.; Ionia (Mich.); Iosco (Mich.: Township); Irish Hills (Mich.); Iron County (Mich.); Iron Mountain (Mich.); Ironwood (Mich.); Island Lake (Livingston County, Mich.); Ithaca (Mich.); Jackson (Mich.); Jonesville (Mich.); Kalamazoo (Mich.); Kensington (Mich.); Kewadin (Mich.); Kingsford (Mich.); L'Anse (Mich.); Chemung, Lake (Mich.); Lake City (Mich.); Lansing (Mich.); Lapeer (Mich.); Laurium (Mich.); Leland (Mich.); Leoni (Mich.); Leslie (Mich.); Lexington (Mich.); Lickleys Corners (Mich.); Lighthouses--Michigan.; Linden (Mich.); Litchfield (Mich.); Lowell (Mich.); Ludington (Mich.); Lyons (Mich.); Mackinac Island (Mich.); Mackinac Island (Mich.); Mackinaw City (Mich.); Macon (Mich.); Manchester (Mich.); Manistee (Mich.); Manistique (Mich.); Maple Rapids (Mich.); Marine City (Mich.); Marion (Mich.); Marquette (Mich.); Marshall (Mich.); Mason (Mich.); Masonic temples--Michigan.; Memphis (Mich.); Michigamme (Mich.); Midland (Mich.); Mills--Michigan.; Monroe (Mich.); Monuments and memorials--Michigan.; Morenci (Mich.); Moscow (Mich.); Mount Clemens (Mich.); Mount Pleasant (Mich.); Muir (Mich.); Munising (Mich.); Muskegon (Mich.); Narrow Lake (Eaton County, Mich.); Negaunee (Mich.); New Hudson (Mich.); Newaygo (Mich.); Newberry (Mich.); Niles (Mich.); North Adams (Mich.); Northville (Mich.); Norvell (Mich.); Norway (Mich.); Olivet (Mich.); Onaway (Mich.); Onondaga (Mich.); Ontonagon (Mich.); Ortonville (Mich.); Osceola (Mich.); Ossineke (Mich.); Otsego (Mich.); Owosso (Mich.); Oxbow (Mich.); Oxford (Mich.); Palms Book State Park (Mich.); Parades and processions--Michigan.; Parma (Mich.); Parshallville (Mich.); Paw Paw (Mich.); Petoskey (Mich.); Pettyville (Mich.); Photographers--Michigan.; Pinckney (Mich.); Pinconning (Mich.); Pittsford (Mich.: Township); Plainwell (Mich.); Plymouth (Mich.); Pontiac (Mich.); Port Austin (Mich.); Port Huron (Mich.); Portland (Mich.); Railroads--Michigan.; Railroad stations--Michigan.; Raisin Center (Mich.); Rawsonville (Mich.); Rexton (Mich.); River Rouge (Mich.); Roads--Michigan.; Rochester (Mich.); Rogers City (Mich.); Roscommon (Mich.); Royal Oak (Mich.); Rudyard (Mich.); Saginaw (Mich.); Saint Clair (Mich.); Saint Ignace (Mich.); Saint Johns (Mich.); Saint Joseph (Mich.); Saint Louis (Mich.); Saline (Mich.); Sandusky (Mich.); Sault Sainte Marie (Mich.); Schoolcraft (Mich.); Schools--Michigan.; Sharon (Mich.); Shepherd (Mich.); Shiawasseetown (Mich.); Shingleton (Mich.); Spring Mill (Mich.); Springport (Mich.); Springville (Mich.); Squawfield (Mich.); Standish (Mich.); Stanton (Mich.); Sturgis (Mich.); Tawas City (Mich.); Tecumseh (Mich.); Tekonsha (Mich.); Thompson (Mich.); Three Oaks (Mich.); Three Rivers (Mich.); Transportation--Michigan.; Traverse City (Mich.); Troy (Mich.); Trenton (Mich.); Unadilla (Mich.); Utica (Mich.); Vermontville (Mich.); Victoria (Mich.); Washtenaw County (Mich.); Waterloo (Mich.); Wayland (Mich.); Wayne County (Mich.); Wellston (Mich.); West Branch (Mich.); White Cloud (Mich.); White Pigeon (Mich.); White Rock (Mich.); Winans, Edwin B., 1826-1894.; Woodbury (Mich.); Wyandotte (Mich.); Ypsilanti (Mich.)
Genre Terms:
Photographs.
- Kodak numbered series
  - Negatives 1-600
    - 1931 (Box 1)
      (neg. nos. 1-32)
    - 1932 (Box 1)
      (neg. nos. 33-270)
    - 1933 (Box 1)
      (neg. nos. 271-559)
    - 1934 (Box 1)
      (neg. nos. 561-600)
  - Negatives 601-1550
    - 1934 (cont.) (Box 2)
      (negative nos. 601-852)
    - 1935 (Box 2)
      (negative nos. 854-1101)
    - 1936 (Box 2)
      (negative nos. 1102-1272)
    - 1937 (Box 2)
      (negative nos. 1273-1305)
    - 1938 (Box 2)
      (negative nos. 1306-1473)
    - 1939 (Box 2)
      (negative nos. 1474-1550)
  - Negatives 1551-2500
    - 1939 (cont.) (Box 3)
      (negative nos. 1551-1651)
    - 1940 (Box 3)
      (negative nos. 1659-1792)
    - 1941 (Box 3)
      (negative nos. 1793-2043)
    - 1942 (Box 3)
      (negative nos. 2044-2126)
    - 1943 (Box 3)
      (negative nos. 2143-2205)
    - 1944 (Box 3)
      (negative nos. 2206-2273)
    - 1945 (Box 3)
      (negative nos. 2276-2289)
    - 1946 (Box 3)
      (negative nos. 2330-2343)
    - 1947 (Box 3)
      (negative nos. 2383-2446-2430)
    - 1948 (Box 3)
      (negative no. 2446)
    - Unnumbered: Brownsville, Michigan covered bridge (Box 3)
- Leica numbered series
  - Roll 1 March-April 1936 (Box 4)
    (nos. 1-37)
  - Roll 2 April-May 1936 (Box 4)
    (nos. 37-73)
  - Roll 3 May 1936 (Box 4)
    (nos. 74-110)
  - Roll 10 June 1936 (Box 4)
    (nos. 341-376)
  - Roll 12 July 1936 (Box 4)
    (nos. 377-413)
  - Roll 13 August 1936 (Box 4)
    (nos. 414-449)
  - Roll 14 October-November 1936 (Box 4)
    (nos. 450-486)
  - Roll 15 November 1936-January 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 487-521)
  - Roll 16 February-April 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 522-558)
  - Roll 17 April-May 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 559-571)
  - Roll 18 May 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 572-610)
  - Roll 19 June 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 611-646)
  - Roll 20 June 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 648-685)
  - Roll 21 June 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 686-723)
  - Roll 22 June-July 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 724-763)
  - Roll 23 July-August 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 764-798)
  - Roll 29 September 1937 (Box 4)
    (nos. 988-1026)
  - Roll 30 October 1937-March 1938 (Box 4)
    (nos. 1027-1058)
  - Roll 31 March-May 1938 (Box 4)
    (nos. 1059-1096)
  - Roll 34 July-September 1938 (Box 4)
    (nos. 1191-1213)
  - Roll 35 September 1938 (Box 4)
    (nos. 1214-1243)
  - Roll 36 September 1938 (Box 4)
    (nos. 1244-1276)
  - Roll 37 September 1938 (Box 4)
    (nos. 1279-1312)
  - Roll 38 September-October 1938 (Box 4)
    (nos. 1313-1349)
- Photograph albums
  - "Michigan Historic Places," 1935-1940 (Box 5)
  - "Around Lake Erie in Ontario. Trip to Chicago Century of Progress," 1933-1939, 279 photographs (Box 5)
  - "Michigan Courthouses," 1932-1940, 115 photographs (Box 5)
    includes state capitol and a few photos of Mount Vernon
  - "Michigan Ships, Monuments, Historic Places, Buildings, Creek Scenes," 1935-1948, 157 photographs (Box 5)
  - "Indian and Trail Markers," 1927-1936, 88 photographs (Box 5)
    (includes memorials and post offices)
  - "Around Michigan: Historic Places, Buildings, Mills, Dams, Bridges, Masonic Buildings," 1931-1936, 197 photographs (Box 5)
    (includes typewritten descriptions of Tulip Time in Holland, 1937, White Chapel, 1932, The Cascades, 1932, Old Mill Dam near Dryden, Mich., 1932, Polar Bear Monument, 1932, Ambassador Bridge, 1932, Bath, Mich. School House, 1932, Walker Tavern and Barns at Cambridge, Mich., 1932, Boulder at Tecumseh, Mich., 1932, Boulder East of Hudson, Mich., 1932, H.S. Earle Memorial, Alma, Mich., 1932, Soldiers Monument, Grand River; Boulders Monument, Hastings, Mich.; Shiawassee Square; The Stone Bell Tower, Baseline Methodist Episcopal Church near Battle Creek; Twin Towers, Irish Hills; New Masonic Home, Alma Mich., photo by Wm. R. Ladner; Old Hudson Mills School House; The Carleton School, Marshall, Mich.; The Pennington School, Macon, Mich.)
  - "Michigan Governors' Homes, Michigan Trees, Old Buildings of Michigan," 1927-1947, 131 photographs (Box 5)
  - Loose album pages 1931-1947 includes Lakewood Zoo near Holland, Detroit Zoo, Kellogg Bird Sanctuary, 117 photographs (Box 5)
  - Miscellaneous prints, 2 folders (Box 5)
Related Material
Prior to his collection coming to the library, Beach had given Claude Stoner many of his negatives dealing with Michigan railroads. Stoner probably incorporated many of these photographs in his collection (also available at the library).
Geographic index
The Geographic index is arranged alphabetically by city, town or geographic area and cites the negative number(s) all negative related to the term. Occasionally addition descriptive information is provided. There may be two sequences of numbers; the first is for the Kodak negatives, the second for the Leica negatives.
Ada
1214
Adrian
194-5, 438, 528, 846, 2013.
Leica Nos. 998 (tablet)
Acme
Leica No. 1312 (Grave of William Leith)
Alberta
Leica Nos. 1271-1274 (Logging related)
Albion
930
Allegan
Leica Nos. 86-87
Allen
Leica No. 619
Alma
217
Alpena
1404
Ann Arbor
22, 268 (Court House), 269 (Masonic Temple), 735-736, 866, 888, 1490-1492, 2029, 2159.
Leica Nos. 548-549, 997 (tablet-Ann's Arbor), 1021 (Baird Carillon), 2069
Athens
1290
Leica No. 1337 (Pioneer tablet)
Atlas
1286
Bad Axe
Leica Nos. 786-789 (tablet, Court House, Masonic Temple, old school)
Baldwin
1787
Battle Creek
122, 124-125, 230-232, 451-452, 791-793, 1466, 1487-1488.
Leica Nos. 564-566 (tablets and monuments)
Bay City
163-164, 529-534, 613-616 (Masonic bands), 1683-1684, 2071
Belding
525
Benton Harbor
643
Bessemer
1422-1423
Beulah
1551
Big Rapids
1448-1450, 1788.
Leica Nos. 1331-1334 (Ferris Institute, 1st house)
Birmingham
58
Blaney Park
1415
Leica Nos. 1219-1222 (Logging Museum and Paul Bunyan)
Brighton
32, 48, 51, 225, 591-593, 2042-2047.
Leica No. 516 (State Police Barracks)
Burns
1313; Leica Nos. 490-492 (Shiawassee Grange Hall, river and bridge)
Byron
69, 1632, 2057
Cadillac
1299, 1543
Leica Nos. 605-608 (Depot, American Legion, Bridge)
Calumet
Leica No. 1268 (Louis Agassiz monument)
Cambridge
134-137
Canada
805-806, 1527-1529
Leica Nos. 414 (Point Pelee), 1348 (Sarnia Tunnel), 1349 (Uncle Tom's Cabin, Dresden, Ontario). [see also Walpole Island]
Capac
1261
Cass City
Leica Nos. 562 (tablet), 563 (Cheney Park)
Cassopolis
732
Centreville
600-601, 1396
Charlevoix
1445.
Leica Nos. 1308-1309 (Light house and bath house)
Charlotte
90, 229, 2052, 2064.
Leica No. 465 (hospital)
Cheboygan
Leica Nos. 1209-1210 (Freak tree)
Chelsea
448, 1082
Chesaning
349
Chicago, IL
728
Clarenceville
480
Climax
598-599
Clinton
133, 1083, 1205
Cohoctah
89, 250-252, 867
Coldwater
184-185, 608-610, 2002.
Leica No. 528 (trail tablet)
Constantine
2020-2021
Copper Harbor
1431.
Leica Nos. 1257-1267
Corunna
121
Cross Village
1556
Croton
Leica Nos. 592-594 (Power house and dam)
Crystal Falls
Leica 1230
Dearborn
236, 295, 493-511 (Greenfield Village), 1209-1210.
Leica Nos. 437
Deer Creek
Leica No. 1064 (old mill in ruins)
Delhi
Leica No. 29-30
Delta
Leica No. 560 (cemetery)
Detroit
172-174, 275-276 (Ideal Home of 1933), 295, 481-489 (Belle Isle), 1241-1242, 1454.
Leica Nos. 415-416, 640-743 (Shriners Parade), 1003 (WWJ), 1004 (SS Edw. Townsend, St. Clair River), 1338 (Cass Monument)
Dexter
1078, 1798, 1957-1968, 1970, 2012, 2031-2034.
Leica No. 27
Dimondale
Leica No. 1034 (Hull Monument)
Dowagiac
1536-1538
Dryden
202-203
Dukes
1438
Dundee
Leica Nos. 62-63 (Ford Mill)
Dunsville
1530-1531
DuPlain
1243
Durand
Leica No. 369 (Circus wreck monument)
Eagle Harbor
Leica Nos. 1250-1256
Eagle River
1429-1430
Leica No. 1245-1247
East Lansing
902-906, 1073.
Leica Nos. 535-537 (Falls)
East Tawas
1075-1077
Eaton Rapids
2402-2403.
Leica Nos. 507 (Horner Bros.), 1032 (Trail boulder south of)
Edenville
1585-1595
Elsie
1244-1247
Escanaba
1419
Esrey Park
Leica Nos. 1265-1267
Farmington
492, 1682
Flat Rock
1253
Flint
206-208
Fort Wilkins
1432-1433.
Leica Nos. 1260-1264 (signs and gates)
Fowlerville
54, 306-307, 314, 336, 544, 576-577, 582, 1217-1232 (Centennial), 1272-1273, 2141-2142.
Leica Nos. 377-380 (train wreck), 387-411 (Centennial), 527 (Old hotel), 1013-1020 (Pere Marquette Wreck), 1050-1051 (Snedicor's), 1194-1195 (ruins)
Frankfort
1548, 1999-2000
Fruitport
Leica No. 766 (World War tablet)
Galesburg
123
Gettysburg, PA
Leica Nos. 341-356 (Civil War monuments)
Gladwin
2072.
Leica Nos. 776-666 (Court House)
Glen Eden Park
Leica Nos. 615-616
Glen Lake
4
Goodrich
317-318
Grand Haven
514-517, 746-750
Grand Ledge
1095-1096, 1674-1675, 1956
Grand Rapids
130-132, 518, 540-542, 743-745 (Norton Mounds), 1541.
Leica Nos. 385-386?, 1347 (Civic Auditorium)
Grayling
1302, 2429
Green Oak
1791
Greenville
191, 526, 1477, 2023-2024
Grindstone City
Leica Nos. 793-794 (shore and rocks)
Grosse Ile
368, 801
Hamburg
594-595
Harbor Beach
Leica No. 790 (tablet)
Harrison
Leica No. 775 (Court House)
Harrisville
1403.
Leica Nos. 1204-1207 (Fire engine, Paul Bunyan, Observatory)
Hart
1296
Hartland
353, 763, 1291-1292, 1808.
Leica Nos. 572-576 (mill)
Hartwick Pines State Park
Leica Nos. 612-613
Hastings
126-127, 589.
Leica No. 91, 995
Hersey
1447
Hi-land
Leica Nos. 422-427
Hillsdale
186, 832-833.
Leica No. 552 (GAR tablet)
Holland
105-116.
Leica Nos. 76-85
Homer
519.
Leica No. 745 (Barry house)
Horton
1359-1360
Houghton
1427.
Leica No. 1269 (copper)
Howell
1-2 (Beach home), 14-17, 21, 26-70, 73-88 (Trucks downtown), 94-95, 102-104, 117-120, 128-129, 139-140, 154-159, 171, 209-210 (County Fair), 219-221, 226-227, 234-235, 237-239, 241, 244-249 (road building), 253-262, 265-267, 270-274, 277-281, 284-291, 294, 296-305
315, 319-326, 335-340; 346-356, 359, 365, 436, 446-449, 457-460, 491, 538, 551-561, 565-575, 578-581, 583, 587, 617-620, 738-740, 838-862
870-875, 895-897, 1089-1094, 1097-1123, 1196-1200, 1215-1216, 1248, 1250-1258, 1274-1276, 1294-1295, 1304-1310, 1316-1329, 1351, 1361-1362, 1400-1402, 1467-1474, 1489, 1533-1535, 1540-1542, 1628
1651-1673, 1695, 1812-1814, 1954, 1971, 1994, 2010, 2015-2018, 2027, 2048-2051, 2054-2062, 2073-2126, 2143-2158, 2160-2207, 2211-2259, 2268-2286, 2330-2343, 2383-2390, 2430.
Leica Nos. 1-21, 33-39, 43-48, 59-60, 417, 433, 440, 446-449, 451-464 (Masons-laying cornerstone new P.O.), 468-486, 509-515, 517-521 (Mr. Beach and cameras), 522, 553-559, 561, 579-586, 796-798, 1007-1008, 1026, 1039-1049, 1056-1058, 1070-1072, 1196-1199 (Catalo Car)
Hubbell
1428
Hudson
18-20, 98, 1637
Hudson Mills
193, 1079-1081.
Leica Nos. 22-26
Huron City
911.
Leica Nos. 791-792 (Phelps residence; church)
Indiana
932, 1202.
Leica Nos. 620-623
Ionia
189-512, 539, 1689-1690
Iosco Twp.
357, 2065
Irish Hills
99-101.
Leica Nos. 495-506 (Stations of the Cross), 782-784 (Tower, Crucifix, Mission)
Iron County
Leica 1231-1238
Iron Mountain
1421
Ironwood
1424-1425
Island Lake
188
Ithaca
545.
Leica No. 774 (Trail marker)
Jackson
180-181, 233, 282-283, 734, 1676, 1995.
Leica Nos. 617, 488
Jonesville
Leica No. 618
Kalamazoo
453, 796-798.
Leica Nos. 568-571 (tablets), 567 (Civil War Monument), 578 (Michigan Central Depot tablet)
Kensington
588
Kewadin
1310-1311 (Gray monument and logging wheels)
Kingsford
Leica 1228
L'Anse
1434-1435.
Leica No. 1270 (Baraga County Court House)
Lake Chemung
96, 742, 1458-1460
Lake City
1300. Leica Nos. 611. See also Hartwick State Park
Lansing
61-62, 228, 240, 263-264, 330-331, 584-586, 628-637, 1280-1282, 1475-1476, 1478, 2022, 2287-2289.
Leica Nos. 370, 534 (tablet), 538-540 (Truck wreck), 541 (mill) 1191-1193 (circus), 1200-1201 (zoo)
Lapeer
204, 1485-1486, 2014
Laurium
Leica 1244
Leland
2001
Leoni
310-311.
Leica 508 (Old Dorm)
Leslie
Leica 487 (church)
Lexington
1950-1951
Lickleys Corners
1668
Linden
1293.
Leica No. 577 (mill)
Litchfield
900
Lowell
513
Ludington
1294, 1997-1998.
Leica Nos. 597-599 (tablets and crosses)
Lyons
364, 1262, 1636
Mackinac Island
1557-1577
Mackinaw City
1408-1410, 1578-1581.
Leica Nos. 1211-1213 (Fort Michilimackinac marker and tepee, Museum building)
Macon
97, 1463, 2063
Manchester
1800
Manistee
3, 1298, 1544.
Leica Nos. 600-604 (trees, bridges, tablets)
Manistique
1416-1417
Maple Rapids
Leica No. 765 (Elijah Ellsworth)
Marine City
1259
Marion
1805
Marquette
1437
Marshall
91-93, 308, 799, 928-929, 1277, 1451.
Leica Nos. 40-42, 746-747
Maryland
Leica 107-110 (Civil War monuments)
Mason
187, 868-869, 1493-1496.
Leica Nos. 1202-1203 [Mason-Dansville Electric Line Memorial]
Memphis
1631
Michigamme
1436
Midland
213-214
Monroe
176-177, 803.
Leica Nos. 523-524 (1st trading post), 1027-1028 (Court House and Cannon)
Monroe County
199
Morenci
Leica Nos. 999-1000 (Stair Auditorium, Taft Bridge)
Moscow
Leica 489 (Old M Tavern)
Mount Clemens
Leica Nos. 529-531 (1st residence and two tablets), 589-591 (Court House, Masonic temple, M.E. Church)
Mount Pleasant
215-216.
Leica 419-420
Muir
Leica 444
Munising
1439.
Leica Nos. 1279-1290 (Pictured Rocks, Tannery Falls, Miner Castle)
Muskegon
751-758.
Leica Nos. 768-771 (Blockhouse)
Narrow Lake
Leica 1033 (Horner tablet)
Negaunee
Leica Nos. 1275-1276 (mine marker and rocks)
New Hudson
863
Newaygo
1640-1641.
Leica Nos. 595-596 (Trophy and county court house)
Newberry
1440-1441.
Leica Nos. 1292-1293 (logs)
Niles
729-730, 1539, 2446
North Adams
360
Northville
343
Norvell
2035
Norway
1420
Ohio (state of)
198, 436, 437, 777-790.
Leica Nos. 50-52 (Napoleon), 53-54 (Defiance), 64-71, 93-98, 361-368 (Civil War monuments), 749-763, 988-991, 1001-1002 (Defiance), 1074-1085 (Columbus and trains), 1094-1095 (Newcom Tavern, Dayton)
Olivet
927.
Leica 1336 (park sign)
Onaway
1582
Onondaga
327
Ontonagon
1426
Ortonville
316
Osceola
1807, 1810-1811
Ossineke
2428
Otsego
Leica No. 88
Owosso
212, 562, 768-772, 1279, 2260-2267.
Leica Nos. 544-547 (tablets), 764 (wheel in tree), 1035-1038 (friends)
Oxbow
764
Oxford
169
Palms Book State Park
Leica 1223-1228
Parma
Leica 450
Parshallville
443.
Leica 1052-1055 (ruins, Parshallville Dam), 1065-1067 (bridges)
Paw Paw
640-642
Petoskey
1444, 1554-1555
Pettyville
242
Pinckney
926.
Leica 438-439 (auto accident)
Pinconning
Leica 779-780
Pittsford
931
Plainwell
Leica 89-90 (Hicks Park)
Plymouth
24, 344, 1206-1208.
Leica 434-435, 587-588 (tablets)
Pontiac
201
Port Austin
Leica 795 (old brick chimney)
Port Huron
477-479, 908, 1260, 1330-1336, 1455, 1482-1484.
Leica 442-443, 1005-1006 (bridge piers)
Portland
622.
Leica 996
Raisin Center
1464
Rawsonville
222-224
Rexton
1414.
Leica Nos. 1218 (DAR Monument)
River Rouge
Leica 526 (Memorial tablet)
Rochester
537
Rogers City
11, 12, 1583-1584
Roscommon
1301
Rose Center
2030
Royal Oak
172, 535-536, 596
Rudyard
Leica 1301
Saginaw
162, 521-524, 881, 2011.
Leica Nos. 1009-1012 (Convict ship and Columbus Day Floats)
St. Clair
907
St. Ignace
8, 1411-1413.
Leica Nos. 1214-1217 (fish nets and ships), 1304-1307 (Park with Algonquin wagon)
St. Johns
218, 759, 1263-1264, 1358, 1649-1650.
Leica Nos. 445, 494, 773 (anchor)
St. Joseph
645-648, 2398-2401
St. Louis
1642
Saline
1084-1085
Sand Lake
Leica 1135 (Marker, Gorden Park)
Sandusky
Leica 785
Sault Ste. Marie
9, 1442-1443.
Leica 1294-1300
Schoolcraft
1288
Sharon
Leica 428-429
Shepherd
1996
Shiawaseetown
161
Shingleton
Leica 1291